So we sit down at the table and probably the hostess will give us some menus if not maybe our waiter
所以我们坐在桌旁，如果不是我们的服务员，可能女主人会给我们一些菜单
or our waitress will come over and introduce themselves and they'll say I'll be I'll be your waitress
或者我们的女服务员会过来介绍自己，他们会说我会成为你的女服务员
your waitress this evening I'll be your waitress this evening.
今晚你的女服务员今晚我将成为你的女服务员。
And then she'll probably or he will probably if it's a waiter give you a menu or some menus.
然后她可能会或他可能会，如果是服务员给你一个菜单或一些菜单。
If for some reason they don't get menus you could say you could say could we look at some menus please.
如果由于某种原因他们没有得到菜单，你可以说你可以说我们可以看看一些菜单。
Could we look at some menus please.
我们可以看看一些菜单吗？
No I think you probably know what a menu is but a menu is the book that you look at which has all the
不，我想你可能知道什么是菜单，但菜单是你看的那本书，里面有所有
food.
食物。
There are a lot of vocabulary words related to a menu entrees desserts appetizers all of these are very
有很多与菜单主菜甜点开胃菜相关的词汇，所有这些都非常
common words but really I want to make sure you're comfortable with how to interact in this situation
常用词，但我真的想确保您对在这种情况下如何互动感到满意
the words themselves are pretty easy to learn.
单词本身很容易学习。
Could we have some menus please.
请给我们一些菜单。
Or she gives us the menus and she says can I.
或者她给我们菜单，她说我可以。
And this is a very common way to say it.
这是一种非常常见的说法。
It's almost always exactly the same.
它几乎总是完全相同。
Can I start you off with anything to drink.
我可以先让你喝点什么吗？
It always starts with a drink.
它总是从一杯饮料开始。
Right.
正确的。
So maybe we just want water and if we do we'll just say that just water for me.
所以也许我们只是想要水，如果我们这样做了，我们只会说这对我来说只是水。
Now you you might not want to order for the other person you are with so you could just say for me just
现在你可能不想为和你在一起的其他人订购，所以你可以只为我说
just water for me.
只是给我水。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Now I can say just water instead of I'd like to have a glass of water here because I'm directly responding
现在我可以说只是水，而不是我想在这里喝一杯水，因为我直接回应
to the question Can I get you something to drink.
我可以请你喝点东西吗？
If someone says Can I get you something to drink.
如果有人说我可以请你喝点东西吗？
And I say I would like a glass of water that's fine but because I'm responding directly if I say just
我说我想要一杯水，这很好，但因为如果我说只是，我会直接回应
water we'll just have water that's also OK.
水 我们只要有水，也可以，也可以。
So this is a common way to respond to this sort of question.
所以这是回答这类问题的常用方法。
And if we want to add something we could say for now thanks just water for now things.
如果我们想添加一些我们现在可以说的东西，现在只感谢水。
What that means is right now I want to drink water as I'm maybe looking at the menu.
这意味着我现在想喝水，因为我可能正在看菜单。
And then once I've decided what food I'm going to get what food I'm going to order maybe what dishes
然后一旦我决定了我要吃什么食物我要点什么菜也许是什么菜
I want then I can maybe order something else to drink maybe a Coca-Cola some sort of soda or perhaps
我想然后我可以点别的东西喝，也许是可口可乐，什么苏打水，或者也许
some wine whatever else I might want.
一些我想要的酒。
So for now suggests that I probably I will get something else but it doesn't mean I have to.
所以现在建议我可能会得到其他东西，但这并不意味着我必须这样做。
But I probably will get something else to drink.
但我可能会喝点别的东西。
So if I do want something else I'll say Can I Can I get a Coke please OK and then you can add and with
所以如果我确实想要别的东西，我会说 Can I Can I get a Coke please OK 然后你可以添加和
no ice with no ice or extra ice whatever.
没有冰没有冰或额外的冰。
OK.
好的。
She says OK I'll be right back with those.
她说好的，我会马上回来的。
I'll be right back with your drink.
我马上回来拿你的酒。
OK.
好的。
Maybe though you want alcohol you'd like to drink some alcohol and you're not sure what alcohol they
也许虽然你想喝酒，但你想喝点酒，但你不确定他们喝的是什么酒
have.
有。
So you might say something like could we could we.
所以你可能会说我们能不能。
Same sentence as we did with the menus.
与我们对菜单所做的相同的句子。
Could we look at the the wine list.
我们可以看看酒单吗？
And then once we decide we look at the wine list if we want to order wine now for alcohol.
然后，一旦我们决定如果我们现在想订购酒来购买酒水，我们就会查看酒单。
Now alcohol alcohol is maybe red wine white wine beer maybe whiskey maybe vodka or a cocktail perhaps
现在酒精酒精可能是红酒白葡萄酒啤酒可能是威士忌可能是伏特加或鸡尾酒
maybe a cocktail.
也许是鸡尾酒。
All of these things are called alcohol.
所有这些东西都被称为酒精。
Alcohol wine is usually just red and white made from grapes just to be clear that's what
酒精酒通常只有红白两色由葡萄制成的红色和白色只是为了清楚这就是什么
wine is.
葡萄酒是。
Alcohol is a broad category which includes every kind of drink like this on the wine list at the top.
酒精是一个广泛的类别，包括顶部酒单上的每一种饮料。
There's often something that says House red and house white.
经常有一些东西说House red和house white。
This doesn't mean that this is the best wine at the restaurant.
这并不意味着这是餐厅里最好的酒。
The house is the restaurant.
房子就是餐厅。
If you ever hear the phrase on the house on the house that means that you don't need to pay it's free.
如果您曾经在房屋上听到房屋上的短语，这意味着您无需支付它是免费的。
For example if your food is an hour late and you waited and you're starving they say Oh I'm so sorry
例如，如果您的食物迟到了一个小时，而您等了又饿了，他们会说哦，我很抱歉
for you know waiting.
因为你知道等待。
Everything is on the house.
一切都在房子上。
They'll pay for your meal.
他们会支付你的餐费。
It's on the house.
它在房子上。
So if you see House red house white basically what that means is this is our basic wine.
所以如果你看到House red house white基本上意味着这是我们的基本酒。
This is the wine that we recommend.
这是我们推荐的酒。
It's usually not super expensive maybe not the cheapest but close to the bottom.
它通常不是超级昂贵，也许不是最便宜的，但接近底部。
It's sort of like their standard.
这有点像他们的标准。
It's sort of like their standard wine.
这有点像他们的标准酒。
So here comes the waitress with the drinks.
于是，女服务员端着酒来了。
Here's your wine here's your Coca-Cola Here's your water whatever.
这是你的酒，这是你的可口可乐，这是你的水。
Oh thank you so much.
哦，非常感谢。
Course you can just say thank you.
当然，你可以说谢谢。
Say thanks.
说谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
And then she'll usually ask you ready to order.
然后她通常会问你准备好点菜了吗？
Are you ready to order.
你准备好点菜了吗。
Have you decided what you'd like.
你决定好你想要什么了吗？
Sometimes she'll say have you decided.
有时她会说你决定了吗？
And then if you haven't decided what should you say you're still thinking right you're still thinking.
然后，如果你还没有决定应该说什么，那么你仍然在思考，你仍然在思考。
So that's what you should say.
所以这就是你应该说的。
That's the common phrase actually.
这其实是一句俗语。
Actually we're still thinking we're still thinking we're still thinking please could you please could
其实我们还在想 我们还在想 我们还在想 请你能不能
you please give us another minute could you please give us another minute could you please give us another
请再给我们一分钟，请再给我们一分钟，请再给我们一分钟
minute.
分钟。
We need a minute.
我们需要一分钟。
The one that I usually use is not quite not quite simply a lower case cube.
我通常使用的并不是一个小写立方体。
Not quite.
不完全的。
We or I are still thinking I am still I'm still thinking I'm still thinking.
我们或我还在想我还在想我还在想我还在想。
And then you could add could you please give me another minute.
然后你可以补充一下，请再给我一分钟。
That's OK if you put both of those together.
如果你把这两个放在一起就可以了。
That's not a problem.
这不是问题。
Still thinking Could you please give us or give me another minute.
还在想你能不能给我们或再给我一分钟。
No problem.
没问题。
Then she'll say OK sure I'll check on you in a couple minutes or.
然后她会说好的，我会在几分钟内检查你，或者。
Sure no problem.
好没问题。